我叫巴里·艾伦
My name is Barry Allen,
是现今世上速度最快的人
and I am the fastest man alive.
在外人看来
To the outside world,
我只是个普通的鉴证专员
I'm an ordinary forensic scientist.
但在尖端科研实验室的朋友们的帮助下
But secretly, with the help
我秘密地打击犯罪
of my friends at S.T.A.R. Labs,
寻找跟我一样的超能力者
I fight crime and find other meta-humans like me.
但是我在时间中迷失了
But I became lost in time.
我的朋友们用尽了一切办法
It took everything in my friends' power
才把我救回来  但我们的世界
to bring me back, and in doing so
也因此出现了新的威胁
our world was opened up to new threats.
我是唯一来得及阻止他们的人
And I'm the only one fast enough to stop them.
我是闪电侠
I am the Flash.
《闪电侠》前情回顾
Previously on "The Flash"...
这是我从神速力出来的地方
This is where I came out of the Speed Force.
一波暗物质也和你一起冲出来了
And a wave of dark matter washed out with you.
迪沃精心策划了一切
DeVoe orchestrated everything to get the people
为了得到公交上的人
he wanted on the bus.
他为什么需要他们的力量
But why does he need their powers?
我猜不出他想干什么
I can't figure out his end game.
这是个计划家  和斯旺一样
We got a planner, just like Thawne.
那我宣布巴里·艾伦上诉驳...
I hereby deem Barry Allen's appeal deni--
等等
Wait!
-迪沃  -不是迪沃
- DeVoe? - Not DeVoe.
是拉尔夫
It's Ralph.
即刻释放巴里·艾伦
Barry Allen is hereby ordered release immediately.
有些人觉得你不应该回到警局
Some people don't think you should be back on the force.
你觉得我什么时候能回来
When do you think I can come back?
所有人都相信迪沃真的活蹦乱跳的时候
When everyone believes DeVoe is really alive and well.
我把它称为思考帽
I call this my thinking cap.
他只想要公交车上的超能力者
He only wants the bus metas.
他想要他们的超能力  所有那些人
He wants their powers. All of them.
我们认识一个公交车上的超能力者
We know a bus meta.
世上还有三个人需要我们的帮助
There's three more people out there who need our help,
我们得在迪沃之前找到他们
and we need to find them before DeVoe does.
如果
What if...
如果我打开缺口  让那3个
What if I just, like, breach all three
公交车上的超能力者去地球2呢
of the bus metas to, like, Earth-2?
这样怎么样
How about this?
我们改变每个公交超能力者的DNA
We alter each bus meta's DNA
通过进行细胞间的外科手术
by performing intercellular surgery.
然后怎样  把他们变成小鸡吗
And what? And turn them into chickens?
对
Yeah.
我们不是毁了无辜人生活的科学怪人
We're not Frankensteining innocent people.
拉蒙  迪沃想要他们的身体
Listen, Ramon, DeVoe wants these bodies.
对不对  也许我们可以把身体换掉
All right? Maybe if we change the bodies,
这些人就安全了
we keep these people safe.
打断下  你不是有6个博士学位吗
I'm sorry, don't you have, like, six PhDs?
-7个  -哪一个学位是疯狂科学
- Seven. - Yeah, which one of them is in mad science?
疯狂科学只是研究的一个领域
Mad science is just an area of study.
不是一个学位  好吗
It's not a degree, okay?
还有  我没看到你提出
And by the way, I don't see you coming up
任何想法
with any other ideas.
知道为什么吗
You know why?
因为在地球1现在是睡觉时间
'Cause it's bed time over here on Earth-1.
你知道睡觉时间是什么意思吗
Do you know what bed time is?
-地球2有这么一说吗  -睡觉时间
- Do they have that on Earth-2? - Bed--Bed time.
是一个我们停下活动
All right, it's this thing where we just shut down
给身体充电的时间
to recharge our batteries.
-天呐  -我很推荐
- Oh, my gosh. - I highly recommend it.
-哈里  -你还在啊  干嘛
- Harry. - You're still here? What?
无论你想到什么  迪沃都先你一步想到了
No matter what you think, DeVoe's already thought of it.
所以不如回家
So why don't you just go home,
充个电  明早再开始  好吗
recharge, start again in the morning, all right?
我要继续
I'm gonna keep going.
晚安
Good night.
也许你已经想到一切了
Maybe you have thought of everything.
就和斯旺一样
Just like Thawne.
闪 电 侠
第四季
第十六集
这是什么
What is all this?
只是让我们可以比迪沃聪明的
This is gonna give us the edge we finally need
突触          反射              算法
基于现实的可预见性运算法则
最终需要的突破口
to be smarter than DeVoe.
实际上  应该说是让我比迪沃聪明的突破口
Or me to be smarter than DeVoe, actually.
看看
Take a look at this.
那是什么
What is that?
这是智力助推器
This is an intelligence booster.
你让德比戴上
You put this thing on Dibny here,
就算是他  也能理解
and even he would be able to understand
点源理论
the point source construction.
而给真正的天才戴上
You put it on a real genius,
最终会让他比思考者更睿智
I'll finally be able to outthink the Thinker.
我不太确定这个思考帽
You know what, I'm not sure this thinking cap
是不是你有过的最棒的主意
is the best idea you've ever had.
这是智力助推器
It's an intelligence booster.
和思考帽看着很像
It looks like a thinking cap.
你不喜欢  就怪自己吧
You don't like it, blame yourself.
-是你给了我主意  -什么
- You gave me the idea. - What?
是你说迪沃像斯旺一样计划了这一切
You're the one that said DeVoe planned all this
好阻止巴里
just like Thawne in order to stop Barry.
而且你说过迪沃变成思考者的那晚
And you said that DeVoe became the Thinker the same night
你成了闪电侠  所以我黑进了
you became the Flash, and so I hacked into
那晚的安全监控录像去看他怎么做到的
security footage of that night to see how he did it.
这就是他那么聪明的原因
This is why he's so smart.
迪沃用神经化学工程助推了他的智力
DeVoe boosted his intelligence with neurochemical engineering
能量来源于粒子加速器爆炸
powered by the dark energy
产生的暗能量
from the particle accelerator explosion.
如果我们做出了自己的助推器  我们也可以做到
And if we build our own, we can do the exact same.
等等  你想要用100亿焦耳的暗能量
Wait, you wanna blast your brain with 10 billion joules
炸自己的脑子吗
of dark energy?
我曾利用过粒子加速器爆炸
I've harnessed energy from
产生的能量
the particle accelerator explosion before,
我还能再做一次
and I can do it again.
但哈里  重新建造你大脑的
Yeah, but Harry, reengineering your brain's
神经化学  这...
neurochemistry, that's--
迪沃做到了
DeVoe did it.
我也可以
So can I.
在我们最终阻止迪沃前还有多少超能力者要丧命
How many more metas have to die before we finally stop DeVoe?
我不会死  我是说...
Not--Not me. I mean...
我是说这是我们努力的目标  对吧
I say we go for it. Right?
对吧  大伙
Right, guys?
你怎么想
What do you think?
我们探索试试
I say we explore it.
我同意
Yeah, I agree.
拉蒙
Ramon.
不  太冒险了
No, this is way too risky.
当然冒险  但如果我们成功了
Of course it's risky, but if we succeed,
我们就可以救那仅存的4个公交超能力者
we will save the lives of the four remaining bus metas,
包括我们团队的一员
including a member of our team.
你说的可是用数量相当大的暗能量
You're talking about intense amounts of dark energy
冲击你的大脑
going right into your brain,
冲击那个帽子
right into that cap,
那会把一个酷爱奶酪的和平主义者
that turned a mac and cheese loving pacifist
变成一个杀人疯子
into a homicidal maniac.
你戴上那帽子  会让你怎么样
You put that cap on, what's it gonna do to you?
我测算过很多次数据了
I've run the numbers dozens of times.
数学和化学的结果都出来了
The math and the chemistry check out.
我可以做到
I can do this.
我觉得你不行
I don't think you can.
有你的帮助我就可以
I can with your help.
这次不行
Not this time.
我们再多想一些办法解决问题
All right, let's keep coming up with more ways to solve this.
我想要弄清楚  终于有人想到办法
Just so I'm clear on this, someone finally came up
阻止那个坐在沙发上的疯子
with a way to stop this La-Z-Boy riding lunatic
我们却不去尝试吗
and we just might not do it?
真是棒棒啊
That's really cool, guys.
-我去劝劝他  -谢了
- I got this one. - Yeah, thanks.
这是唯一的办法
This is the only way.
有没有他的帮助  我都要做
I'm gonna do it with or without his help.
拉尔夫
Hey, Ralph.
别担心  好吗
Look, don't worry, okay?
我们会想办法解决的
We're gonna figure this out.
对  大家一直这么说
Yeah, everybody keeps saying that,
而且每次我们就要拿下迪沃了  他都脱身了
and each time we almost get DeVoe, he gets away.
每次他脱身
Every time he gets away,
都离抓到我更近了一步
he's one step closer to getting me.
不会这样的
Hey, that is not going to happen.
我再也不能冒这个险了  爱瑞丝
Well, I can't take that chance anymore, Iris.
所以如果任何人要找我  我都在楼下
So if anyone needs me, I will be downstairs
我的小客房里呆着  直到这一切结束
in my tiny guest quarters until this is over.
外面还有3个公交上的超能力者
There are still three bus metas out there,
我们需要你的帮助找到并保护他们
and we're gonna need your help to find them and protect them.
爱瑞丝  从现在起  我唯一需要保护的人
Iris, the only person I need to protect from now on
就是老好人拉尔夫
is good old Ralphie boy.
你是团队的一员
You are part of this team.
对  而且我是唯一一个迪沃
Yeah, and I'm the only one with a body that DeVoe
想要夺取身体的人
is trying to snatch.
你对我出去有多少危险
You don't have any concept of how dangerous it is
根本没概念
for me out there.
我有概念
Yes, I do.
你怎么会有
How could you?
因为我是团队的队长
Because I'm the leader of this team.
是啊  你是
Yeah, that's right, you are.
但你总是安然无恙地躲在那里
But you're always back there hiding safe and sound.
而与此同时  我们剩下的人却在第一线
While the rest of us are out in the field
置生死于不顾
putting our lives on the line.
抱歉我迟到了
Hey, sorry I'm late.
表层发生了一些争执
Some drama in the Cortex.
谢谢你点的咖啡
Thanks for the coffee.
没事的
It's all good.
你还好吗
You okay?
还好  你知道的
Yeah, yeah, I'm, you know--
塞西尔在晚期妊娠阶段了
Cecile's in her third trimester,
所以一定要很谨慎了
so it's definitely getting serious.
你们选好名字了吗
You guys have any names picked out yet?
选了一些
Uh, yeah. A few.
别藏着了  我不会告密的
Come on, I'm not gonna tell anybody.
你是不会  因为你没秘密可告
No, you're not, because you're not gonna know
除非塞西尔告诉你
until Cecile tells you.
-好吧  -不管怎样
- All right. - Anyway.
我跟辛格谈过让你回实验室的事
I talked to Singh about getting you back in the lab.
是吗  然后呢
Yeah, and?
要等一段时间了
It's gonna be a while.
为什么  我以为汉克森法官
Why? I thought Judge Hankerson
和辛格已经得到所需了
and Singh had everything they needed.
我们也这么以为  但市长她想
We thought so, too, but the mayor wants to sit down
亲自见见迪沃一家
with the DeVoes herself.
真的吗
Seriously?
我们找不到马尔利泽
Look, we can't find Marlize,
所以我们唯一的办法就是让拉尔夫
so the only chance we got is to get Ralph to use
再次用他恶心的能力假冒迪沃
his nauseating powers to impersonate DeVoe again.
好吧  我会去问他的  但现在他
All right, I'll ask him, but right now he'll barely
几乎不会离开尖端科研实验室
leave S.T.A.R. Labs.
你那套伙伴系统怎么
What happened to that whole buddy system thing
行不通了
you had going on?
我猜这对他来说还不够吧
It's not enough for him, I guess.
那我就没辙了  巴里
Then I don't know, Barry.
我应该出去的
I should be out there.
去帮助他人  打击坏人
Helping people. Putting bad guys away.
现在  我们应该尽力阻止迪沃
Right now, we should be trying to stop DeVoe
找出最后那几个车公车超能力者
and finding those last few bus metas.
因为我有种不好的预感
'Cause I got a bad feeling
其中一个很快就要现身了
one of them's gonna show up soon.
下次烧的就是你的手了
Next time, it'll be your hand.
现在  所有人都趴下
Now, everybody on the floor.
哥们儿  你是想找死吗
Dude, you had a death wish?
照他说的做
Do what he says.
偷窃是罪过
Stealing is a sin.
你不应该用得来的能力
You shouldn't be using the powers
做这种事
you've been given this way.
我愿意怎么用就怎么用
I'll use them any way I see fit.
你要是再上前
Including frying you to a crisp
就把你烤成薯片
if you move any closer.
我觉得你不会这么做
Oh, I don't think you will.
你并不想伤害我或是这家银行里的任何人
You don't wanna hurt me or anyone in this bank.
你现在收手还来得及
You can still walk away from this.
但你一旦碰了那笔钱
But the moment you touch that money,
你的人生就永远的改变了
your life changes forever.
你肯定不想这样吧
Now, you don't really want that, do you?
或许你说得对
Maybe you're right.
或许你只是想找死
Or maybe you've got a death wish!
什么鬼
What the hell?
我的超能力
My powers!
都消失了
They're gone!
不  不  不
No, no, no!
兄弟  你是个真正的...
Hey, buddy, you're a real--
英雄
hero.
西斯科
Cisco.
你有什么发现
What do you got?
就是跟平常一样
Oh, you know, the usual.
一堆又一堆的暗物质
Just loads and loads of dark matter.
合情合理  目击者说这个人
Makes sense. Eye witnesses said this guy
用手中发出的火焰烧融了这道闸门
melted this vault door with fire from his hands.
想到了  但不是一般的火焰
Hmm, figures. But not just any fire.
这种火融穿了25厘米厚的强化钢板
This fire melted through ten inches of reinforced steel.
这需要超过3300摄氏度的高温
I mean, that would take over 6,000 degrees Fahrenheit.
是罗里的热风枪输出功率的十倍
Ten times the thermal output of Rory's heat gun.
更奇怪的在后面
Well, here's where it gets weirder.
显然不久之后  他的能力失效了
Apparently shortly after, his powers stopped working.
失效是什么意思
Stopped working?
是啊  所以如果他是一个公车超能力者
Yeah, so if he was one of our bus metas,
我想这一个我们是不用去费心了
I guess we have one less to worry about.
谁的超能力会失效啊
Nobody's powers stop working.
埃里克·弗瑞  六个月前
Eric Fry, six months ago,
你是否在405路公交车上
were you on the 405 bus?
快得了吧
Please.
我看起来像是使用公共交通的人吗
Do I look like someone who takes public transit?
那好吧  弗瑞先生
All right, then, Mr. Fry.
你拥有超能力多久了
How long have you had your powers?
有几年了
A few years.
你是个老司机了
You're an OG meta.
然后就忍到现在才开始使用超能力吗
And you just started using them now?
在这儿是没错
Here, yeah.
闪电侠一现身  我就不再活动了
Once Flash showed up, I took this act on the road.
不过现在都不重要了
Doesn't matter anymore, though.
对  你现在没有超能力了
Right, you don't have your powers anymore.
因为能力就那么消失了  凭空不见了
'Cause they just disappeared? Vanished?
化成一股湮没了吗
Into thin air? Huh?
好了  西斯科
All right, Cisco.
他没问题
He's clear.
你知道能力为什么会消失吗
You have any idea how this happened?
上一刻我还有超能力  下一秒...
One minute I had powers. The next...
什么都没了
Nothing.
你能带他出去吗
Will you get him out of here?
也对  带他出去
That's right. Get him out of here.
-好吧  -好  带他出去
- All right. - Yeah, get him out of here.
我没法相信他的超能力就这么消失了
I can't believe his powers disappeared like that.
人怎么会失去自己的超能力呢
How does someone lose their powers?
我能想到几种可能性
So, I can think of a couple of ways
会导致该情况的发生
this might have happened.
如果这位埃里克·弗瑞是通过转移太阳辐射
If this Eric Fry metastasizes solar radiation
制造热量
to create heat,
我们可以把他放在黑暗环境中使他失去超能力
we could put him in the dark to de-power him.
但现在还是大白天呢
But it was still broad daylight.
好吧  也许他体内的生化系统发生了变化
Okay, maybe his internal biochemistry has been altered
可以自己内燃产生热量
to create its own internal thermal combustion
而他只是用光了燃料
and he just ran out of fuel.
好吧  如果这人不是公车超能力者中的一个
Okay, so if this guy's not one of the bus metas,
那这就意味着在迪沃找上我之前
then that means that there's still three more out there
还有三个超能力者在外游荡
before DeVoe gets to me.
所以我很安全  该说我更安全了
So, I'm safe. Safer, I'm safer.
那些人是无辜的  拉尔夫
Those are innocent people, Ralph.
我也是无辜的  还不是要被终结掉
I'm innocent. I'm still gonna get terminated.
老天啊
Oh, my God.
-我是《终结者》里面的莎拉·康纳  -不
- I'm Sarah Connor. - No.
我要回我房间去了
I'm gonna go back to my room.
吃点东西安抚一下心情
Get some comfort food.
拉尔夫
Ralph...
在我看来  弗瑞走进银行时
The way I see it, Fry walks into the bank
还有超能力  见到了另一个人之后
with his fire powers, meets this other guy,
他的能力就没了
and then his powers are gone.
是巧合吗  我不觉得
Coincidence? I think not.
你是说这个人对弗瑞做了什么
So you think this guy did something to Fry?
我觉得我们可以问他几个问题
I think we can ask him some questions.
我跟那家银行里每一个目击者都谈过了
I interviewed every eye witness in that bank.
没人知道他是谁
Nobody knew who he was.
西斯科  不如你把今天的储蓄记录
Cisco, why don't you crosscheck the deposits
和爸爸的目击名单交叉对比一下
from today with dad's witness list?
早想到了
Way ahead of you.
名单上的每个人都对上了  除了马修·金
Everyone on the list checks out except Matthew Kim--
他是中城总医院的急救人员
an EMT out of Central City General.
巴里  咱们该去问问题了
Barry, let's go ask some questions.
我去吧
Oh, I'll go.
巴里  你可以留在这儿
Barry, you can stay here.
好吧
Okay.
我从没出去执行过任务
Well, you know, I never go out into the field,
所以我想...
so I thought, you know...
好吧  反正你说了算
Yeah, I mean, you're the boss.
好吧  凯特琳
Okay. Uh, Caitlin,
不如你研究一下
why don't you see
这个盗取超能力是什么原理
how this power stealing thing works,
西斯科  不如你用卫星追踪
and Cisco, why don't you use the satellite's tracking perimeters
排查一下城市中的暗物质
to scan the city for dark matter?
好的
Okay.
要是你们需要我  我就跑来
I'll just come running if you need me.
好的  谢了
Okay. Thanks.
我能在这儿待一会儿吗
Can I hang out in here?
你能...你介不介意...
Can you--Do you mind--
你能不能过会儿再吃东西
Can you save the eating till later?
我们这儿还忙着救命呢
We're actually trying to save lives here.
不过这真的很好吃
This is really good, though.
是吗
Is it?
是啊
Yeah.
这玩意儿你组装起来倒是挺快的嘛
You put this together pretty quick, huh?
是啊  用来试运行的
Yes, I did, for a test run.
我能感到我的神经在加速
I can feel my neurons firing.
速度是平常的二十倍
Firing at a rate 20 times their normal rate.
这还是在没有暗物质的情况下
And that's without the addition of dark matter.
我能感到大脑的处理系统在进化
I can feel my brain's processing systems evolving.
有百分之六十七的可能你会把芥末
There's a 67% chance you're gonna spill that mustard
溅到地板上
on the floor.
好吧  你怎么做到的
Okay, how did you do that?
我只是分析了你的饮食习惯
Well, I simply analyzed your eating habits
并将其外推成了一套行为预测模型
and extrapolated them at a predictive behavior model
只用了四秒钟
all within four seconds.
帽子起作用了
The cap is working.
厉害  但我还是不太相信
Eh, cool, but I'm not quite convinced.
不信
No?
真的吗  你还不信
Really? You're not convinced?
那好吧
All right, then.
答案是否定的
The answer is none.
对你的身体放尊重一点好吗
And have a little more respect for your body, will you?
这是个素热狗  哥们
This is a veggie dog, man.
我说的不是那个素食热狗  哥们
I'm not talking about the veggie dog, man.
我说的是你在裤子上擦芥末的事
I'm talking about the wiping the mustard on the pants
因为从裤子的运动模式可以看出你的身体
causes the pant movement which indicates a lack of clothing
与衣物缺少摩擦  而这只意味着一件事
to bodily friction, which can mean only one thing.
对了  就是我穿什么样的内裤
Right, what kind of underwear am I wearing?
答案是...
And the answer...
没穿
is none.
都是用你那个炫酷的金属帽想到的吗
You got all that from your fancy metal cap?
-是的  -太了不起了  哈里
- Yes, I did. - It's impressive, Harry.
就是有点小瑕疵
Except for one very small thing.
是什么
Which is?
你的脑袋着火了
Your head is on fire.
才没...
It's no--
医疗中心
我说到共度更多时光的时候
When I mentioned spending more time together,
我是说一家人吃烤肉  不是去询问疑犯
I meant family barbecues, not questioning people of interest.
我知道  我只是想让人知道我不害怕
I know, I just want people to know that I'm not afraid
时不时的出来跑跑外勤
to go out in the field every once in a while.
谁说你怕了
Who says you are?
-拉尔夫  -拉尔夫
- Ralph. - Ralph?
他说什么  他都不离开那楼里
He should talk. He won't even leave the building.
我知道  但是引起了我的思考
I know, but it made me wonder, you know?
什么样的领队  只让其他人去冒险
What kind of leader constantly puts everyone else's life
而自己在后边呆着
on the line except their own?
宝贝
Oh, baby.
我们都知道你什么都不怕
We all know you're fearless.
当战场上需要你的时候
Whenever you've been needed on the field,
你就会去
you've gone.
所以别让拉尔夫影响了你
So don't let Ralph get in your head.
抱歉  中城警局
Excuse me. CCPD.
我们在找一个急救专家叫马修·金
We're looking for an EMT named Matthew Kim.
他就在那边过去
Yes, he's right through there.
那边吗  谢谢
There? Thank you.
马修·金
Matthew Kim?
乔·韦斯特警探  中城警局
Detective Joe West, CCPD.
我们想就今早中城银行被袭一事
We'd like to ask you some questions about the attack
问你一些问题
at Central City Bank this morning.
我对那事一无所知
I wouldn't know anything about that.
真的吗  因为我有很多证人
Really? 'Cause I have a dozen witnesses
看到你反抗融掉保险库的那个人
that saw you stand up to the man that melted the vault.
他想要伤害别人
He was going to hurt people.
帮助他们是我的责任
It was my duty to help them.
你为什么一句话不说就离开了
Any reason you left without making a statement?
我需要重新补给装备
I need to finish restocking my inventory
以防又有电话打来
before another call comes in.
我帮不了你
I can't help you.
马修  我们知道你和
Look, Matthew, we know you had something to do
那个银行失去超能力的人有关
with that guy at the bank losing his powers.
我们需要知道  你对他做了什么
We need to know. What did you do to him?
为什么  这样你就可以偷走我的了吗
Why? So you can steal mine?
不  不要
No, no!
-放开她  -放下枪
- Let her go. - Put the gun down.
我说了放下枪
I said put it down.
他不配拥有那超能力
He didn't deserve those powers.
尖端科研实验室
紧急呼叫
他在伤害他人
He was hurting people.
闪电侠
Flash!
不只有你一个人获得了超能力
You're not the only one that's been blessed with powers.
我也在帮助别人
I'm helping people, too.
这样不行
Not like this.
这赖你  可不是我
You did this, not me.
我去抓他
I got him.
我速度丢了
I lost my speed.
你速度丢了是什么意思
What do you mean you lost your speed?
各位  我想我知道丢哪了
Uh, guys, I think I found it.
真是太棒了
This is amazing.
没错
Yeah, it is.
我走了所有能想到的测试
Well, I've run every test I can think of.
心电图  细胞回归综合分析
EKG, cellular regression synthesis,
脑化学  还有暗物质证实了
brain chemistry, and dark matter confirms it.
爱瑞丝是个极速者
Iris is a speedster.
那巴里呢
So, what about Barry?
你身体里的那一部分
Everything that was a part of you--
你的速度  与神速力的连接
your speed, connection to the Speed Force,
暗物质
the dark matter--
现在都是爱瑞丝的一部分了
it's all a part of Iris now.
-你能不能  -逆转吗
- Can you- - Reverse it?
我不知道  可以试试
I don't know. I can try.
所以  马修·金不仅仅是移除基因
So, Matthew Kim isn't just removing DNA.
他会传送给所触碰的人
He's transferring it to anybody he touches.
他不是在消除超能力者
He's not getting rid of metas.
他是在制造新的
He's creating new ones.
不仅仅是这样
Well, that's not the only thing.
猜猜谁的公寓就在405巴士线一个街区远
Guess who's got an apartment just a block away
并且每天都坐着上班去
from the 405 bus line and rides it every day to get to work?
所以马修是巴士超能力者  不是弗瑞
So Matthew is our bus meta, not Fry.
也就是说迪沃早晚回去找他
Which means that DeVoe is gonna come after him sooner or later.
如果迪沃获得了马修的能力
And if DeVoe gets Matthew's abilities,
他就可以夺走我们所有人的能力了
he could take away all our powers.
除非我们先把他拉拢到咱们这边
Unless we get him on our side first.
这样他就可以消除迪沃的超能力基因了
Then he can remove the meta DNA from DeVoe.
-能成功吗  -我觉得可以
- Could that work? - I mean, yeah.
或许能行  据我来看
It could. As best I can tell,
马修的能力是融化
Matthew's abilities work by melting down
基因之间高度浓缩的连接
the highly concentrated bonds between DNA.
让它们变得柔软  这样就可以被抽出
That makes them totally pliable so he can extract them
然后将同样的超能基因注入其他人
and infuse somebody else with the exact same meta DNA.
融掉紧密连接的纽带
Melting highly concentrated bonds.
融点
Melting Point.
对对对  我得记下来
Oh, yeah, yeah, yeah. I gotta write that down.
很好  那么你们就去想办法
Okay, great, so you guys figure out how to get
把这个融点先生和迪沃放到一个屋檐下
this Mr. Melting Point in the same room as DeVoe
并且不让他的脑袋被吸走
and not get his brains sucked out.
我去拿些熊爪饼
I'm gonna go get a couple of bear claws
然后回到我屋里去
and go back to my room.
不是融点先生
It's not Mr. Melting Point.
就只叫融点
Look, it's just Melting Point.
你知道吗  现在某个人
You know, somebody out there
有了弗瑞的能力了
has Fry's fire powers right now.
我们找到他们的紧急性和找马修一样高
We need to find them as much as we need to find Matthew.
交给我吧
I'm on it.
我去看看有没有办法能逆转
And I'll see if there's a way to reverse this.
那么
Well...
在那之前  我们怎么办
Until then, what do we do?
我们训练
We train.
好吧
Okay.
拉蒙  你在...
Ramon! Where--
在这里啊  你在干什么
There you are. What are you doing?
升级些软件
Updating some software.
太好了  就是没事干
Oh, good. So nothing.
真棒  我需要你的帮助
Great, I need your help.
去找拉尔夫
Try Ralph.
拉尔夫太废物
Ralph's useless.
他就知道吃
All he does is eat.
你想要什么
What do you want?
你有没有微纤丝压缩扳手
Do you have a microfilament compression wrench
和钴回收夹钳
with cobalt retrieving clamp?
有
Yeah.
是吗  在哪
Yeah, where is it?
干什么  你要拿去造死亡帽吗
Why, so you can work on your death cap?
-那不是死亡帽  -就是死亡帽
- It's not a death cap. - It's a death cap.
-不是  -我听说地球二有不少工具
- No, it isn't. - I hear there's plenty of tools on Earth-2.
可我在地球一上呢
Yeah, well I'm on Earth-1.
你需要送一程吗
Oh, you need a lift?
我现在就给你开个缺口送过去
I'll breach you there right now!
我说话不这个样
That's not what I sound like!
行吧
Fine.
西斯科  你为什么不帮帮他
Cisco, why can't you just help him?
为什么只有我觉得把一个暴脾气
Why am I the only one who thinks putting a rageaholic
和暗物质放在一起是个坏主意
and dark matter together is a bad idea?
他是想要阻止迪沃
He's trying to stop DeVoe.
这个点子可不坏
That's not a bad idea.
他想要用自己的智力对抗一个可以
He's trying to match his intellect with a mad man
可以把思想来回传送的疯子
whose innovations are warping his brain.
- 你看《蜘蛛侠2》了吗  -没有
- Have you not seen "Spider-Man 2" - No.
你活着还有什么意义
How can you live with yourself?
这或许有危险  但是也可能成
It might be dangerous, but it also might work.
而且我们也基本没有办法了
And we're kind of running out of ideas.
再说了  哈里有没有你的帮助都会去做
Besides, Harry's gonna do this whether you help him or not.
所以也许有办法能做出这个思想帽
So maybe there's some way to make this thinking cap
同时保证他的安全
and to keep him safe.
她速度真快
She can move.
爱瑞丝  也许你应该...
Hey, Iris, you might just wanna--
-我慢不下来  -没关系
- I can't slow down. - That's okay.
你需要慢慢的降低速度
All right, just gradually ramp your speed down,
不然的话你就会...
otherwise you're gonna--
变成这样吗
Do that?
你没事吧
Hey, you okay?
过来
Come here.
我没事  我没事
Yep, I'm straight. I'm straight.
要感谢超级恢复速度啊
Thank God for speed healing, huh?
是啊
Yeah.
我知道这对你来说不容易
Hey, I know this isn't easy on you.
我没事
I--I'm fine.
巴里
Barry...
我就是...
I am. It--
我失去了速度
I lost my speed.
我丢了中城警局的工作
I lost my job at the CCPD.
感觉迪沃在慢慢的把一切从我身边夺走
Just feels like DeVoe is slowly taking everything away from me.
他还没有夺走一切
He hasn't taken everything away.
如果我永远拿不回来了呢
What if I never get it back?
凯特琳会找到办法的  好吗
Caitlin is gonna find something, okay?
在那之前  你只需要看着我  就像是
Until then, you just have to watch me like I've watched you
这三年来我看你一样
these last three years.
我想也只能如此了
Yeah, I guess so.
这可真有点烦人
Wow, that's super annoying.
发生了什么
What's happening?
鲍德温塔起火了  中城消防局去了
Baldwin Tower's on fire. CCFD's responding,
但是顶楼有人他们救不到
but there's people on the top floor they can't reach.
凯特琳  冰霜杀手今天要去灭火了
Okay, Caitlin, Killer Frost is on fire duty.
拉尔夫  西斯科  换衣服
Ralph, Cisco, suit up.
我不去
Yeah, not a chance.
这可能只是迪沃为了骗我们出去的陷阱
This could just be a trap for DeVoe to get us out in the open.
我想我们有个更大的麻烦
Hey, I think we got a bigger problem.
我们没有闪电侠了
We don't have a Flash anymore.
我们有
Yeah, we do.
我觉得她还没有准备好应付这一切
I don't think she's ready for all that.
她刚得到...  你刚获得超能力
I mean, she just got her- You just got your powers.
不  我想去
No. I wanna do this.
好吧  好吧
Okay. Okay, all right.
那我们就在这里看着
We'll monitor from here, then.
好吧  你不能穿着这一套出去
Okay, well, you can't go out there wearing that.
没错
Oh. Right.
抱歉  凯特
Sorry, Cait.
有面具吗
Mask?
等一下
Right.
谢谢  杰西·快客
Thank you, Jesse Quick.
漂亮
Nice.
一定要小心
Please, be careful.
你负责通讯
Guess you're on comms.
对
Yeah.
对对对
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
好  我怎样...
All right, how do I-- How do I--
-另一台监控器  -不是这台
- Other monitor. - Wrong monitor.
我到了  天啊
I'm here. Oh, boy.
爱瑞丝  有五个人被困在了14层
Okay, Iris, there are five people trapped on the 14th floor.
用你最快的速度把他们救出来
Just get them out of there as fast as you can.
-我做到了  -干得好
- I did it. - Great work, okay?
现在回到大楼里救火
Now you gotta get back in there and put out the fire.
好
Right.
各位  我进来了  我要怎么做
Guys, I'm here. What do I do?
你知道怎么做  用你的手臂
You know what to do. Use your arms.
创造一个导风漏斗
Create wind funnels.
把房间里的氧气都吸出去
Suck all the oxygen out of the room.
然后火就会灭了
And the fire will go out.
就像他过去做过的无数次一样
Just like he's done a thousand times.
你能行的
You got this, girl.
火更大了
It's making it worse.
是她转动手臂的方式不对还是
Is she rotating her arms the wrong way or...?
向反方向转
Just go the opposite direction, okay?
爱瑞丝  怎么了
Iris, what was that?
爱瑞丝
Iris!
我的腿被压住了  我动不了
My leg is pinned. I can't move.
你得穿过它
Okay, you have to phase through it.
什么  我不知道怎么做
What? I don't know how.
让你整个身体震动起来  明白吗
You have to vibrate your whole body, okay?
你得去感受它
You just--you have to feel it.
我不行  我动不了  我做不到
I can't. I can't move. I can't do it.
我们快要没时间了  巴里
We're running out of time, Barry.
大楼的框架要撑不住了
The integrity of the room is failing.
天花板就要塌下来了
The ceiling's gonna collapse.
巴里  整幢楼都要塌了
Barry! The whole place is going up.
你还好吗
Are you okay?
-还好  -谢谢
- Yeah. - Thank you.
你的肺还会有点痛
There's still a little bit of irritation in your lungs
因为你昨晚吸入了太多烟
from all the smoke you inhaled last night,
但你马上就会没事的
but you should be good to go soon.
你的腿也已经痊愈了
And your leg's already healed.
不应该让她过去的
Shouldn't have let her go out there.
你还没有准备好
You weren't ready.
我昨晚救了很多人  拉尔夫
I saved a lot of people last night, Ralph.
是  然后西斯科还得去救你
Yeah, and Cisco had to save you.
好了  我们只是需要确认
All right, look, we just need to make sure
这种事情不会再发生了
this doesn't happen again.
我们得找到马修·金
We have to find Matthew Kim
还有那个被他注入埃里克·弗瑞的超能力的人
and whoever he transferred Eric Fry's powers to.
你还需要多久能逆转它
How close are you to reversing this?
-我不确定我能不能做到  -什么
- I don't know that I can. - What?
我一整晚都在尝试能想到的解决方法
I was up all night trying every conceivable solution.
暗物质拼接  DNA克隆规律
Dark matter splicing, pattern DNA cloning,
甚至在细胞程度上
even regrowing meta enhanced stem material
再生超能力增强物质
on a cellular level.
都没有成功
Nothing will work.
我无法复制融点的超能力
I cannot replicate Melting Point's powers.
所以除非我们找到他并让他逆转他做过的事
So unless we find him and get him to reverse what he's done--
那么爱瑞丝就要永久加入极速者队伍
Iris is Team Speedster on a permanent basis.
真是太棒了
Great, that's, uh-- That's great.
我要去写遗嘱了
I'm gonna go work on my will.
拉尔夫
Ralph...
哈里  哈里  我知道你听到我说话了
Harry. Harry, I know you hear me.
又有一名队员被迪沃的超能力者伤到
Another team member hurt by one of DeVoe's metas.
-我知道  -我们能处理好
- I know. - And we can fix it,
-但是  不  -我知道
but, no, no. - I know!
你知道还有什么吗
And you know what else?
昨晚并不是只有斯诺一个人在工作
Snow wasn't the only one who was up all night working.
我昨晚也一直在工作  我快成功了
I was up all night working. I'm almost done.
我就快成功了  但是你不帮我
I'm almost finished, but you won't help me finish!
我会去帮你
I'm gonna help you finish!
-完成  -思考帽
- Finish-- - The thinking cap.
我会帮你完成思考帽
I'm gonna help you finish the thinking cap.
事实上  这是一个智力增强器
It's an intelligence booster, actually.
它叫智力增强器
It's called an intelligence booster.
-两个条件  -你有什么条件
- Two conditions. - What are your conditions?
第一  我们刺激你的突触
- One, we stimulate your synapses
不用暗物质
without using dark matter.
行  不用暗物质  第二个呢
Fine, no dark matter. And two?
《星际迷航:下一代》中反派
一旦你开始像博格的洛丘特一样
The minute you start acting like Locutus of Borg and start
用你的博格椅子同化其他人
assimilating everybody with your Borg chair--
你可以用震波把我送回我的地球  行了吧
You can vibe me back to my Earth. Okay?
-好  -我们走
- Okay. - Let's go.
慢慢来
Take it easy.
这才是第二天
It's just day two.
天啊
Oh, man.
关于跑步这件事你说得对
You were right about running.
相当的平静
It's so peaceful.
安宁
So calming.
让人更容易去思考
Actually makes it easy to think.
你刚得到你的速度
Look, I mean, you just got your speed.
你知道这一点  对吧
You know that, right?
如果你去休息一下的话
I don't think anyone would hold it against you
不会有人责怪你的  就让西斯科和凯特琳
if you took a minute and maybe just let Cisco and Caitlin
去处理这个超能力者  就像以前那样
handle this meta, just run point like always.
我就像之前那样呆在这里
Just stay here like I always do?
不是  我  你知道我不是这个意思
No, I--You know I didn't mean that.
我知道你不是这个意思  但我是
No, I know you didn't. I did.
爱瑞丝  我...
Iris, I--
是因为你觉得  你需要向队员证明
You think that--what, that you need to prove to the team
你不害怕吗
that you're not afraid?
不是向你们所有人证明  是向我自己证明
No, not to all of you. To me.
巴里  我当记者的时候  我经常在战场上
Barry, when I was a reporter, I was always in the field
为了一篇报道让自己身处险境
putting myself in danger for a story.
去年以后
And after last year,
因为一些原因我不再这样做了
for some reason that just stopped.
可能是因为萨维塔
Maybe it was because of Savitar.
可能是因为你进入了神速力
Maybe because you were gone into the Speed Force.
我不知道  但是
I don't know, but...
我辞职了
I quit my job.
加入了这个队伍  现在我大部分时间
I joined this team, and now for the most part,
就呆在这里  而你们都在外面
I just stay here while all of you are out there
冒着生命危险
putting your lives on the line.
因为我们的超能力
Because of our powers.
不  不只是因为这个  巴里
No, it's not just that, Barry.
我拥有超能力之后才明白
And it took me getting these powers to realize it.
但是  现在我是拥有超能力的那个人
But now that I'm the one that has it,
轮到我来做你们一直在做的事了
it's my turn to do what all of you have been doing.
向我自己证明  那个无所畏惧的我
To prove to myself that that fearlessness that I had
还活着
is still in me.
各位  我们找到弗瑞丢失的超能力了
Guys, I think we found Fry's missing powers.
去搞定他们吧
Then go get them.
危险警报
卫星正在以银行抢劫案时相同的强度
Satellite is tracking temperature at the same
追踪体温  所以...
intensity as the bank robbery, so--
他在那
That's him.
那个人是谁
So who's that?
马修·金
Matthew Kim.
金要偷走他的超能力
Kim's gonna try and steal his powers.
好  我们走
All right, let's go.
不  你们呆在这
No. You guys are on point.
我能做到
I can do this.
你确定吗
You sure about this?
我必须做到  巴里
I have to, Barry.
好  但是记住  不能让他碰到你
All right, but remember, he can't touch you.
否则他会把你的超能力也偷走
Or he'll take your powers away, too.
明白
Right.
我不确定这次你可不可以穿我的衣服
Also I'm not sure my clothes are gonna work this time.
这个我能解决
I have a fix for that.
这是我在这么短的时间里能做到最好的了
It's the best I could do on such short notice, though.
多谢  西斯科
Thanks, Cisco.
这不是有衣架吗
I got hangers.
好了  我们走
All right, here we go.
别逼我们开枪  退后
Don't make us shoot you! Stand down!
我可不这么想  条子
Oh, I don't think so, copper.
除非我拿到钱
Not until I get my money!
-这是个错误  -上  抓住他
- This is a mistake! - Down! Down! Take him down!
别开枪
Hold your fire!
你得停手
You need to stop this.
我正想停下呢  兄弟
Oh, I just got going, pal.
等等  你是银行里那个英雄  是吗
Wait, you're that hero from the bank, aren't you?
是我
I am.
我需要你停手
And I need you to stop this.
然后你就可以像拿走他的超能力那样拿走我的
So you can take my powers like you did his?
我可不想这样
I don't think so!
你可刚把它给了我
You just gave them to me.
你在说什么
What are you talking about?
你不知道吗
You didn't know that?
当你拿走他的超能力时
When you took powers from him,
你把它给了我
you gave them to me.
现在  我要去拿他没能拿到的东西
And now I'm gonna get what he couldn't.
钱
Money!
我觉得你今天救的人够多了
I think you've done enough saving for today.
后面让我来吧
I'll take it from here.
我们现在就结束这一切怎么样
How about we just end this right now?
听起来很有趣
That sounds fun.
因为我刚刚只是在热身
'Cause I was just warming up.
怎么了  受不了这个温度吗
What's wrong? Can't stand the heat?
爱瑞丝  你要绕着他跑
All right, Iris, we need you to run around him.
制造一个漩涡
Create a vortex.
氧气不足就会让火熄灭
The lack of oxygen should extinguish the flames.
我没法靠近他
Can't get close to him!
温度高达426摄氏度
Temperature's at 800 degrees.
那得多热啊
Like, how hot is that?
跟岩浆一样热
As hot as lava.
各位  想办法啊
Guys, we need a plan!
我有办法  女士
Oh, I got a plan, lady.
就是在我出大招前把钱还给我
And it's called give me my money before I unleash hell!
那是什么鬼
What the hell is that?
那是热火龙卷风
That is a thermo cyclone.
火会离那些公寓特别近
That fire's gonna get too close to those apartments.
会导致上千人丧生
And thousands of people will die.
怎么办
What do we do?
我们启动这个
We turn this thing on.
-哈里  不  别  -爱瑞丝需要答案
- Harry, no, don't. - Iris needs answers.
-我们还没  -得告诉她答案
- Hey, we haven't-- - She needs answers!
快啊  各位  怎么办
Come on, guys! What do I do?
动手吧
Do it.
巴里  快  给我答案
Barry, come on, I need an answer!
撑住  爱瑞丝  撑住
Hang on, Iris. Hang on.
有4827种办法
There are 4,827 ways this could go,
但只有一种办法可行
and all of those ways will fail except one.
如果爱瑞丝用她的速度从中城湾
If Iris uses her speed to draw enough water
引足够多的水尾随她
from Central City Bay into her wake,
就可以浇灭火焰
she could extinguish that blaze.
你想让她制造浪潮
You want her to create a tidal wave?
只有这个办法
It's our only hope.
爱瑞丝  用最快速度奔跑
Iris, I need you to run as fast as you can.
-在水上跑  -在水上  什么
- On the water. - On the water? What?
跑的时候确保使劲往水下压
Make sure when you run you dig your heels in
以密集的路线来回跑
and you move back and forth in a tight formation.
-为什么  -以便激起尽可能多的水
- Why? - So you drag as much water ashore as possible.
浇灭龙卷风
Put out the cyclone.
你想要我制造三十多米高的浪潮
You want me to create a 100-foot tidal wave?
疯了吗  我做不到
Are you crazy? I can't do that.
你做得到  你说过你过去无所畏惧
Yes you can. You told me that you used to be fearless.
我知道你现在仍然无所畏惧
I know that you still are.
你是我认识的最勇敢的人
You're the bravest person that I know.
你做得到
You can do this.
我知道你可以  我们都知道
I know you can. We all do.
跑吧  爱瑞丝  跑吧
Now run, Iris. Run.
好  就是这样  好  就是这样
Yeah, that's it. Yeah, that's it.
密集的路线  用密集的路线
And then tight formations, okay? Tight formations.
对了  爱瑞丝  继续跑
That's it, Iris. Keep going.
继续跑
Keep going.
都退后
Everybody back!
快闪  快闪  快
Move, move, move, now!
摇滚万岁
Long live rock and roll!
好了
Yes!
干得漂亮
Nice work.
她做到了
She did it.
漂亮  闪电侠
Nice work, Flash.
很抱歉这样对你们
I'm so sorry I did this to you.
我还以为是在清理城市
I thought I was cleaning up the city,
结果却是添麻烦
but I was just making it worse.
我们阻止了他
Well, we stopped him.
他关进铁山监狱了  这才是重点
He's in Iron Heights, and that's all that matters now.
你们确定都想这样做吗
You sure you both wanna do this?
你来决定
It's your call.
不得不说在水上奔跑真的很好玩
I have to say running on water is really fun.
但如果你们想要我回归老位置
But, if you guys will have me back,
我很愿意再次回到控制台
I would love to get back behind the console again.
-当然了  -拜托了  还有谢谢你
- Of course. - Please, and thank you.
准备好了吗
All ready?
好了
Yeah.
-好  -来吧
- Okay. - Here?
好
Okay.
完了吗
That's it?
你没事吧  宝贝
You okay, baby girl?
应该没事
I think so.
那你呢  闪电侠
What about you, Flash?
感觉很棒
I feel great.
英雄归来
My boy's back.
这是我最后一次用这超能力
Well, that's the last time I'm using this power.
城市差点毁在我手上
The city was almost destroyed because of me.
但你也不知道会发生什么
But you had no idea that would happen.
对  别对自己这么严苛  兄弟
Yeah, don't be so hard on yourself, pal.
我以为自己被选中是有更重要的目的
I thought I was chosen for a higher purpose.
这种情况不适合我
This can't be the plan for me.
或许你被选中是有更伟大的目的
But maybe you were chosen for a bigger one.
什么意思
What do you mean?
我们提到的那个人  克利福德·迪沃
The guy we mentioned, Clifford DeVoe,
没找到所有公车超能力者  他不会罢手
he isn't gonna stop until he gets all the bus metas.
就是说我们得阻止他
Which means we have to stop him.
我们需要所有可能的帮手
We could use all the help we could get.
你们确定我能帮上忙吗
Are you sure I can make a difference?
绝对能
Absolutely.
之前迪沃已经显示出不敌其他公车超能力者
DeVoe's shown weakness against other bus metas in the past.
有你帮忙  我们或许真有机会
With your help, we might actually have a chance.
怎么开始
How do we start?
-我带你参观一下  -好
- I'll give you the tour. - All right.
别多心  我可不想没了超能力
No offense. I like my powers, so...
所以巴仔
So, Bar...
你之前没制造过浪潮
You never made your own tidal wave before.
对  没有
No, I haven't.
走吧  姑娘
You go, girl.
怎么样  想来教老人新招数吗
So, what do you say, you wanna teach an old dog a new trick?
好啊
All right.
早上六点训练
Training. 6:00 A.M.
别迟到哦
Ooh, don't be late.
-没问题  老大  -欢迎回归
- You got it, boss. - Welcome back.
拉尔夫
Hey, Ralph.
马修也需要个兄弟
You know, Matthew is gonna need a buddy, too.
这个吗
Well, that's, uh...
前提是他会留下来
That's assuming he stays.
等他发现迪沃得到
After he finds out that DeVoe has gotten everyone
想要的所有人后  他就会害怕
he's come after, he'll be terrified.
跟我一样
Just like I am.
听着  拉尔夫
Look, Ralph,
我懂你现在的感受
I know what you're going through.
不  爱瑞丝  你不懂
No, Iris, you don't.
我懂
Yes, I do.
去年当我以为萨维塔要杀死我时
Last year when I thought that Savitar was going to kill me,
我当时...
I was...
已经被吓疯了
scared out of my mind.
你是怎么处理的
How did you deal with it?
真的很难受
It was really hard.
但后来我发现我要是一直逃避
But then I realized that if I hid from him,
不去面对  那么
if I hid from the world, then...
萨维塔就已经赢了
Savitar had already won.
所以我决定不向恐惧屈服
So I made the decision to not give into the fear.
我选择继续活着
I chose to keep living.
听着
Look, uh...
我之前说你从没想过
What I said before about you never putting your life
牺牲自己
on the line...
我错了
I was wrong.
你是位很棒的闪电侠
You make one hell of a Flash.
不管穿没穿战衣
In or out of the costume.
谢谢
Thanks.
-你要上去了吗  -对
- Are you going up? - Yeah.
我想或许克利福德·迪沃该再次
I think maybe it's time that Clifford DeVoe paid the Mayor
拜访市长了
another visit.
我觉得你从没离开过尖端科研实验室
I thought you were never leaving S.T.A.R. Labs.
我想或许我也该开启新生活了
Well, I think maybe it's time I started living again, too.
而且我们也没有彻底吃完素食热狗
Plus, we're definitely out of veggie dogs.
谢谢你  爱瑞丝
Hey, thanks, Iris.
塞西尔推荐的那家楔石城的店
Fresh from this little place in Keystone
新鲜出炉的
that Cecile recommended.
她对食物的痴迷真是越来越严重了啊
Those cravings of hers are getting really intense, huh?
对  可不是吗
Yeah, tell me about it.
还好我速度快
It's a good I'm speed.
你知道不必放弃自己的速度  对吧
You know you didn't have to give up your speed, right?
我永远不会要求你放弃的
I mean, I would have never asked you to.
我知道
I know.
为什么要放弃
Why'd you do it?
你知道怎样才能成为伟大的极速者吗
You know what makes a great speedster?
不在于他们的速度
It isn't their speed.
而在于当世界陷入黑暗时
It's being the light that everyone needs
世人渴求的光芒
when the world grows dark.
在于他们的为人
It's the kind of person they are.
一直希望帮助他人的为人
The kind of person that always wants to help.
所以你注定就是闪电侠
That's why being the Flash is your destiny.
是你帮助他人的方式
It's your way of helping others.
不是我的
But it isn't mine.
这个才是
This is.
我不打扰你了
I'll leave you to it.
被闪电侠拯救
2018年3月13日  中城大火  事关众人
昨天的火情威胁到我们的家园...
好了  摘掉
All right, take it off!
摘掉  哈里  够了
Take it off, Harry. That's enough.
已经超过你说的安全额度20%了
We're already 20% over your suggested safety limits.
得再多戴一会儿
You've gotta give it a little more time.
不  够了  我要关了
No, that's it. I'm shutting it down.
不不  就快好了  就快好了
No, no, we're almost there. We're almost there!
你可不是"绝命毒师"  洛丘特
You're not "Breaking Bad," Locutus!
好吗  我要断开光子流了
All right, I'm disengaging the photon flow.
好吧
Fine.
我不再需要它了
I don't need it anymore.
你知道名字了
You got the names?
最后两位公车超能力者
The last two remaining bus metas.
珍妮特·佩蒂和艾德文·高斯
Janet Petty and Edwin Goss.